IAN WILLIAMS

Full Stack Software Developer

917-294-8250

□ norbekian9@gmail.com

norbek2003.github.io

780 Riverside Dr. apt. 9B, NYC



Hard working, experienced, and results-driven full stack software developer with 2+ years of experience in the field. Experienced in working with a team to achieve strict goals and return results in a timely, efficient fashion. Dedicated to improving company performance and providing management with efficient tools for running the company. High level of proficiency in Javascript, Python, PHP, and Java. Quick study in new languages and frameworks.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Full Stack Software Developer

Yabla | 2019 - Present

Full Stack Software Developer. Compile and visualize statistical data for the company's financial and administrative departments. Design administrative software to improve management of the service's members and business affiliates. Spearhead new projects and features for the users. Create classes and scripts on the backend to control and manipulate data. Design pages and processes to encourage and ensure healthy habitual use among customers.

Head Of IT Redefy Stuyvesant | 2019 - 2020

Volunteer work creating and maintaining a website for the local chapter of Redefy, a student led activist

Tutor CSDojo | 2019 - 2020

Volunteer work tutoring young students in data structures and algorithms using Python, Netlogo, Lisp, and

Full Stack Software Developer

Stuyvesant Student Union | 2017 - 2019

Designed software for the Union as a member of the IT department. Initiated and spearheaded the development of an escalator monitoring system using own proprietary software and kiosks throughout the campus, making for efficient travel inside the large multistoried complex.

EDUCATION

Graduate of Stuyvesant High School, Class of 2020

345 Chambers St, New York, NY

Graduated one year early from Stuyvesant High School, one of the US's most renowned public schools, due to an accelerated academic program.

Weighted GPA: 4.2

Relevant Courses

- AP Computer Science AB: Introductory College Course on Data Structures and Algorithms.
- Artificial Intelligence: College Course on the uses and ramifications of AI, as well as how to develop it.
- System Level Programming: College Course on working on a low level with C.
- · Computer Graphics: College Course on the algorithms behind visual engines.

SKILLS

Technical

Object-Oriented Design

Design And Implement Database Structures

Advanced Data Structures And Algorithms

Rapidly Learn New Languages And Frameworks

Lead And Deliver Complex Software Systems

Proficient In Git And Other Industry Standard Tools

Personal

Effective communicator

Team player

Problem solver

Good time managemer

LANGUAGES

Front: HTML, CSS, Javascript

Back: Python, PHP, Java, C

Database: MySQL

INTERESTS

Cycling

Playing Guitar and Singing

Science Fiction

History and Politics